[Music]
good morning uh it's a great honor to be
here with you to talk about the power of
digital transformation and driving you
know business value
uh you know over the past year this uh
you know pandemic
a once in a century uh challenge it has
really driven home the message
of the importance of technology and how
you know companies and businesses are
adopting technology to really drive
uh you know a transformation in their
business process their customer
experience their journey
it is safe to say that you know this
pandemic has really accelerated the
digital transformation journey by at
least 10 years if not more
and in a country as populous as rich as
diverse
um as india you know technology becomes
way more important than ever
uh during these challenging times uh
it's been
you know our honor and our pleasure to
be partners with icici
lombard you know the largest private
non-life insurer in
india uh to look at their digital
journey using azure and azure ai
garish welcome and thank you for your
time today
thank you for uh having me here let's
start with the
you know the the journey you're on as
the leader you know on the forefront of
understanding
uh the challenges your customers face
the optimization of your operations and
really servicing
you know a very very large country like
india during this pandemic
you know with the power of technology
i'd love to you know hear your thoughts
uh as a leading private sector
uh non-life insurer as you said uh we've
also been on the forefront of adoption
of digital
uh we are part of for the icsa bank
group and icc bank group was a
private bank which kind of uh
revolutionized banking in
uh india more than 20 years back by
getting him
internet banking atms and a whole lot
uh way back in uh 2013 was when we first
took it is to move on to uh the azure
cloud for our test and development
environment that partnership has really
uh
grown well over a period of time not
only did we move our
test dev we went into our or the entire
productivity suite within a year after
that
we moved on to uh the microsoft platform
as a insurance player we have a large
tele calling set up i mean that's
one of the key channels of selling
insurance we have over
a thousand early callers who are calling
customers uh
for various uh uh products now uh
as a part of any telecalling setup you
obviously have a quality assurance
service that you uh provide normally we
are able to do about 20
sampling of calls in our discussions
with
microsoft team they said why don't you
look at using ai to do a bit of this and
when you look at the peculiarities of
our situation and
this is what you really mentioned about
india being a vast country and
not only do you have multiple languages
uh purity of language also is not not
given so you don't have a call which is
entirely in english you don't have a
call which
could be entirely in hindi renault's
data science team work with
the microsoft engineering team to kind
of create
nlp algorithm to interpret the responses
and build a fuzzy match logic uh to help
in improving the
uh custom model built uh we currently
have
managed to to get it to about 70 plus
accuracy
in terms of uh uh the recognition so
and and what that does is that kind of
takes the
uh problem to a different level now uh
we are able to do
uh screening 100 of the calls which
would have been impossible so you are
able to mix the ai
and the human to do something far better
than what
only a human factor could do out there
first i mean um thank you for choosing
azure and azure ai and and you know part
of our scale part of our
uh investment you know globally in terms
of coverage is around data sovereignty
it's great to hear that that is adding
value to businesses such as yourself
how do you see the kind of the road map
going forward you know duration in terms
of future services and ideas
you know as you drive the transformation
going forward one of the problems it
wanted to look at was promoter clips
right
we need to identify whether what is the
kind of extent of damage what is the
clear
what is the uh whether it's a repair
replace
so this is a very complex problem we are
able to crack bits of it
i mean you crack half the problem you
you kind of are able to identify whether
it's a
dent or a damage uh you are still not
able to figure out whether you need
how whether you need to repair it or
replace it but just this is good enough
for
us to address another issue that we are
facing right
they uh when a motor policy lapses uh
and you don't renew it in time
uh you normally need to have your car
inspected
to see whether there is a you picked up
in the time it was
insured before you kind of renew that
insurance so uh and that process usually
takes about 24 to 72 hours
that problem of having that inspection
done at any point in time
having looking at pictures of the car
and being able to identify whether there
is a dent or damage in the car if
there's no dental damage you can issue
the policy
right off it reduces the time from like
i said 24
7 to us to just about uh three to five
minutes is what time it takes for the ai
to process the images
and come back with the solution
fascinating i mean first of all i mean
thank you for being a pioneer and also
uh to your point i mean the journey the
thousand mile journey starts with the
first step and i think the fact that
you've
uh understood the assets that you've got
you know we've got a bunch of images
what do we do with them how do we
leverage them to really deliver business
value
and you know applying technology to
transform that you know
at a ahead of the curve you know has now
benefited your business and now
it really has driven uh you know strong
roi better customer engagement and
you know going from three days to three
minutes i mean that's
pretty incredible to hear thanks good to
see uh the
range of possibilities with the ai plus
hi
going forward thank you garish for your
time today really appreciate it and
thank you for your partnership and your
business and
looking forward to expanding the
relationship and the partnership with
many many new use cases thank you again
thank you thanks thank you
you